Crunch is solving
the coordination problem.
The scale that they have among this
huge community of data
machine learning engineers.
All of the value creation
is happening
today.
They're using
the tools of decentralized markets
and stable coins to
create a broad community
to generate better real world outcomes
than the best of the best
data science team.
it's just built
in the open.
Bounds for talent:
limitless.
When we look at what type of teams
we want to
bring into the Solana incubator
the first thing we always start with is
founder.
Jean had been working on this problem
and this design space
for years prior to
AI becoming interesting and exciting.
Jean is the type of founder where
any time of day
he's pinging you
he's working with his team.
The dynamism of Jean
on the one hand
his ability to form
good partnerships
and then on the other side
the remainder of the team:
a real technical know-how.
foundational layer
in how
organizations solve problems.
Period.
Any institution out there
has data challenges.
And if you can be the one-stop shop
to power solutions
and insights on those data
you can really scale your company
almost infinitely.
Anybody
around the world can participate in this
and it could be
that we're giving somebody
a better future
because they can find
a job
and be rewarded
through a marketplace like Crunch.
Egalitarian.
Catalyst.
Internet's open
machine learning infrastructure.
Catalyst for building this
internet native future.
It allows
businesses who wouldn't necessarily
have access to
machine learning talent and models.
To access that in an open
and permissionless environment.
What Crunch is enabling is
fundamentally something that is
a counter to
the concentration effects that
you see across AI.
AI is touching so many different
areas of our economy
But Crunch is laser focused on this
notion of
how do we actually help
institutions with their
machine learning challenges.
And then for companies
who maybe have a few
machine learning engineers
but they want to take their insights
to the next level
look into Crunch
and see how it can help you
drive solutions for your business.